advantage.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Advantage Rent A Car

* * *

Last modified: August 19, 2013 

**Introduction**

At Advantage Rent A Car (“Advantage”), we are committed to protecting your privacy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website “advantage.com” (our “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information. If you do not agree with any of the terms of this privacy policy, please do not use this Website.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * on this Website. 
  * in e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website. 

It may not apply to information collected by: 

  * Information gathered at the rental location, via the claims process (accident related), via the roadside assistance (breakdown related), customer service process, call center interaction (recorded calls). 
  * through any other means, including on any other website operated by Advantage or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries). 

Advantage recognizes the privacy protections afforded to individuals in the European Union (“E.U.”) and Switzerland with regard to personal data (as defined below) in connection with the transfer and protection of “personal data” received from the E.U. Advantage has subscribed to and complies with the voluntary U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor program and the voluntary U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor program (the “Safe Harbor Frameworks”), in accordance with the E.U. Directive 95/46/EC established by the European Commission and the Swiss Federal Act on Data Protection (collectively, the “Data Protection Directives”) by adopting and implementing the privacy principles set forth in this Privacy Policy (the “Principles”).

 “Personal data” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person (or legal person, in the case of the Swiss Safe Harbor Framework) (a “data subject”), where an identifiable person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity. Data that is publicly available in some countries is subject to regulation in others. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, personal data does not include information that has been anonymized, encoded or otherwise stripped of its identifiers, or information that is publicly available, unless combined with other non-public personal data.

The following Principles serve to provide notice that Advantage will ask you to provide personal data if you create an account or use the Website. Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information, including your personal data, and how we will treat it. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This privacy policy may change from time to time, as explained further below. 

**Data and Use**

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect personal data and non-personal data to facilitate and provide services you request from us and for our operational uses in connection with such services, which data may include: 

  * Name, address and contact details, including telephone and mobile number and e-mail; 
  * Date and place of birth, passport number and driver’s license number; 
  * Employer(s) name and address; 
  * Credit card information; 
  * Frequent flyer and other membership reward program information; 
  * Affiliations with companies or associations; 
  * Limited static location data such as geographic location where the auto is picked up and dropped off, where any automated toll payments have been made should the customer utilize automated toll payment, parking tickets and/or traffic violations, vehicle impounding or towing and the location of electronic devices used to contact us. 
  * Information regarding the vehicle and its operation during your rental; 
  * Rental charges you incur and other information relating to your transactions; and 
  *  Information about your credit history or other publicly available information about you from consumer reporting agencies. 

**We collect this information:**

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us. 
  * Via automobiles that you rent from us, automated toll payment devices, municipalities issuing tickets/violations, companies involved in the towing or impounding of the vehicle. 
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies. 
  * From third parties, for example, travel agents or brokers, social networks, consumer reporting agencies, and other companies that we have relationships with, such as our affiliates and business partners. 

**Usage Details, IP Addresses, Cookies and Other Technologies.**

To improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, we may automatically collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions and patterns, including: 

  * Details of your visits to our Website including the pages and resources that you access and use on the Website. 
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type. The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include: 
  * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. 
  * Web Beacons. Pages of our the Website and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit Advantage, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an e-mail and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). 

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal data: 

  * To present our Website and its contents to you. 
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us. 
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it. 
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection. 
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide through it. 
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information. 
  * For any other purpose with your consent. 

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may share your information with companies you use in connection with your rental, including personal data as authorized, including the following: 

  * Your credit card provider and other companies that process your charges; 
  * Any company or organization that is paying all or part of your rental charges; 
  * Any intermediary you use, such as a travel agent or broker, in relation to any aspect of your rental; and 
  * Any operator of a membership program for which you are rewarded for renting with us, such as a frequent flyer program. You may quote a special discount code when you rent with us, entitling you to the special rate or benefits we may have negotiated with your company, association, credit card company or travel club. 

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction. 

We may disclose personal data that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy, and with respect to E.U. and Swiss individuals, in accordance with the Principles: 

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates. 
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business. 
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Advantage’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal data held by Advantage about our Website users is among the assets transferred. 
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an e-mail address to use the “e-mail a friend” feature of our Website, we will transmit the contents of that e-mail and your e-mail address to the recipients. 
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information. 
  * With your consent. 

We may also disclose your personal data: 

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request. 
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes, or to recover vehicles. 
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Advantage, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [ PersonalData@Advantage.com](mailto:PersonalData@Advantage.com). 

**Other Rights**

We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information: 

Tracking Technologies and Advertising: You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. 

Targeted Advertising: If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form). You can also always adjust your user advertising preferences in your account profile by checking or unchecking the relevant boxes or by sending us an e-mail. 

We will only use your personal data for our marketing purposes or those of third parties with your prior consent. 

If you do not receive marketing messages from us and would like to do so, or if you want to limit or restrict our mailings or sharing of your data for marketing purposes, please send an e-mail to [ marketing@advantage.com](mailto:marketing@advantage.com).

**Choices about How We Use and Disclose Your Information for E.U. and Switzerland Residents**

The following Principles serve to provide notice to E.U. and Switzerland residents that Advantage transfer personal data you provide outside of the E.U. or Switzerland, as applicable, to Advantage. Advantage is a member of the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework. Advantage complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Advantage has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/

Advantage will not use personal data for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the E.U. or Swiss individual unless the individual affirmatively and explicitly consents (“opts-in”) to the processing, or unless an exception applies. Should the information collected be “sensitive” personal data, Advantage will not disclose such information to a third party or use it for any purpose other than for which it was originally collected unless you opt-in to Advantage doing so. Advantage also provides E.U. and Swiss individuals with the opportunity to withdraw consent at any time (“opt-out”) of their information being used for a purpose other than for which it was originally collected or when such information is to be disclosed for the first time to a third party, in which case their personal data will not be further processed. If at any time after providing personal data to Advantage, you decide to opt-out of Advantage’s use of your personal data, you may contact Customer Service or e-mail us at [PersonalData@Advantage.com](mailto:PersonalData@Advantage.com). 

**Access and Correction:** Upon written request to Advantage, Advantage will provide individuals in the E.U. and Switzerland with reasonable access to their personal data. Advantage will also take reasonable steps to allow E.U. and Swiss individuals to review their information for the purposes of correction their information. There are certain limitations to the Access and Correction rights, as set forth in the US Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor website. (http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/)

Advantage employs reasonable methods to ensure that any personal data held about E.U. and Swiss individuals is accurate, complete, current and otherwise reliable in relation to the purposes for which the information was obtained. Advantage collects personal data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for the purposes for which it is to be processed. E.U. and Swiss individuals have a responsibility to assist Advantage in maintaining accurate, complete and current personal data about them. 

If you believe that any personal data provided to Advantage is incorrect, or is, has been, or might be used inappropriately, please contact us at PersonalData@Advantage.com, and we will take steps to correct the information as appropriate. 

**Onward Transfer:** If Advantage transfers personal data to a third party that is acting as an agent, Advantage will do so only if Advantage verifies that the third party (a) subscribes to the Safe Harbor Principles and has certified its compliance, and is accordingly independently responsible for complying with the Safe Harbor requirements; (b) is subject to the Data Protection Directives or another adequacy finding; or (c) Advantage has entered into a written agreement with such third party requiring that the third party provide at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the relevant Principles. 

Adherence by Advantage to these Principles may be limited (i) to the extent required to respond to a legal or ethical obligation; (ii) to the extent necessary to meet national security, public interest or law enforcement obligations; and (iii) to the extent expressly permitted by an applicable law, rule or regulation. 

**Data Security**

We have implemented reasonable measures designed to secure your personal data from accidental loss and from loss, theft, destruction, unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions and account information will be encrypted using SSL technology. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the storage and processing of digital information and transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee its security. Any transmission of personal data is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. 

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

You agree to review the terms of use each time you access and use this Website and to be bound by such terms of use as are in effect at the time when you access this Website. Advantage reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy and the Principles at any time. By accessing this Website, you agree that Advantage may provide notice to you of such modifications by posting them on the Website. Advantage will notify affected individuals of such modifications in accordance with applicable law and the Safe Harbor Framework, as applicable. It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal data, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address specified in your account and/or through a notice on the Website home page and as required by law. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes. 

As long as Advantage continues to store, use, or disclose personal data transferred to Advantage under the Principles, Advantage will apply to such personal data either the Principles or safeguards that provide no less privacy protection than the applicable Safe Harbor Framework then requires. 

**Contact Information**

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Advantage commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Advantage at [PersonalData@Advantage.com](mailto:PersonalData@Advantage.com)

 Advantage has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Advantage, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at [ www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint. 

Advantage has in place procedures for training employees in the internal mechanisms for handling complaints and their implementation, and disciplining employees for failure to follow such mechanisms. Advantage also has in place internal procedures for periodically conducting objective reviews of compliance with the above. ws of compliance with the above. 

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: 

1052 Highland Colony Parkway, Suite 204, Ridgeland, MS 39157 

[info@advantage.com](mailto:info@advantage.com) or via our toll-free number: 800-777-5500.
